<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:c="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.cellview.client">
<g:HTMLPanel styleName="gwt-AccessConfigurationSheet">
<h1>Configure Site Access</h1>
<h4>Users access the site either</h4>
<ul><li>anonymously (i.e., as the <em>anonymousUser</em>), or</li>
<li>via a Google account, using OpenID (requires an Email account (e.g., user@gmail.com)), or</li>
<li>via an Oauth 1.0 or Oauth 2.0 token (issued by Google with access to userInfo.email), or</li>
<li>via an ODK account, with a username and password that a site administrator has configured for them.</li></ul>
<h4>Capabilities are as follows:</h4>
<ul><li>Data Collector - able to download forms to ODK Collect and submit data from ODK Collect to ODK Aggregate.
<br/>Only ODK accounts and the <em>anonymousUser</em> can be granted Data Collector rights.
<br/>The <em>anonymousUser</em> must be granted Data Collector rights to accept submissions from unidentified sources (e.g., from ODK Collect 1.1.5 and earlier,
 or from ODK Collect 1.1.7 and later if not authenticating).</li>
  <li>Data Viewer - able to log onto the ODK Aggregate website, filter and view submissions, and generate
   csv or kml files for download.</li>
   <li>Form Manager - all the capabilities of a Data Viewer plus the abilities to upload a form definition,
   delete a form and its data, and upload submissions manually through the ODK Aggregate website.</li>
   <li>Synchronize Tables - able to download, upload and alter data records within ODK Tables as restricted by table-access privileges granted to the user.</li>
   <li>Administer Tables - able to administer tables and table-access privileges from the ODK Tables website.</li>
   <li>Site Administrator - all the capabilities of a Form Manager plus the ability to add users,
   set passwords, and grant these capabilities to other users.</li></ul>
<h3>Edit Users</h3>
<p>Change usernames, delete usernames, grant capabilities and set passwords for ODK accounts below.</p>
<c:CellTable ui:field="userTable" />
<br/>
<g:CheckBox ui:field="anonymousAttachmentViewers">Allow anonymous
retrieval of images, audio and video data (needed for GoogleEarth balloon displays)</g:CheckBox>
<p/>
<g:Button  styleName="gwt-Button" ui:field="button" text="Save Changes" />
<hr/>
<h3>Add Users</h3>
<p>Enter the usernames (for ODK accounts) or e-mail addresses (for Google OpenID accounts) to add to the
list of users in the above table</p>
<g:TextArea visibleLines="3" characterWidth="80" ui:field="addedUsers" />
<br/>
<g:Button styleName="gwt-Button" ui:field="addNow" text="Add"/>
<br/>
<hr/>
<br/>
</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
