<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:c="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.cellview.client">
	<g:HTMLPanel>
<div align="CENTER"><h1>Configure Site Access</h1></div>
<p>Use this page to configure who has access to this server.
This page allows you to designate individuals as any of:</p>
<ol><li>site administrators - people who can configure site access.</li>
<li>form administrators - people who can add or delete forms and delete
uploaded submissions, or</li>
<li>submitters - people who can download and upload forms and upload,
view, download and publish submissions.</li></ol>
<p>Users are identified by their ODK Aggregate usernames.
For ease of data entry, if you cut-and-paste e-mail addresses into
the fields below, the usernames of the email addresses will be taken to be
the ODK Aggregate username for that individual.  Individual e-mail
addresses should be separated by
whitespace, commas or semicolons; in general, you should be able to
cut-and-paste the To: line from your
e-mail program into the box below, and things should work fine.</p>
<p>E-mail addresses can be of either form:</p>
<ul><li>mitchellsundt@gmail.com</li>
<li>"Mitch Sundt" &lt;mitchellsundt@gmail.com&gt;</li></ul>
<p>Alternatively, if you simply enter usernames separated by
whitespace, commas or semicolons, the system will create those usernames
without any associated e-mail address.</p>
<p>If you enter duplicate usernames or two or more e-mails that collapse to
the same username, only one ODK Aggregate username will be created.</p>
<hr/>
<h2>Site Access</h2>
<h4>User Password</h4>
<p>Authenticated submissions from ODK Collect 1.1.6 (or higher) require the use
of passwords that are held on this server and that are specific to this server
(referred to as <em>Aggregate passwords</em>).
Site administrators can set or change Aggregate passwords by visiting the 
<em>Manage User Passwords</em> tab. By default,
users are not assigned an Aggregate password
and so will not be able to do authenticated submissions until a site administrator
assigns them a password or until they log in and set their own password.</p>
<p>If usernames are associated with gmail accounts, users with those accounts
can log into the website using OpenID.  Otherwise, users can only
log in with their Aggregate password. For those users, a site administrator must
visit the above link to set an Aggregate password before they can gain access
to the system.</p>
<p>Users, once logged in, can reset their Aggregate passwords by visiting 
the <em>Change Aggregate Password</em> tab.</p>
<h4>Add Users</h4><p>Enter the usernames or e-mail addresses to add to the
list of users below</p>
<g:TextArea visibleLines="10" characterWidth="80" ui:field="addedUsers" />
<br/>
<g:Button styleName="gwt-Button" ui:field="addNow" text="Add"/>
<br/>
<hr/>
<h4>Edit Users</h4><br/>
<g:Label ui:field="errorMessage" styleName="error_message" visible="false"/>
<c:CellTable ui:field="userTable" />
<br/>
<hr/>
<br/><br/>
	<g:CheckBox ui:field="anonymousSubmitters">Accept submissions from
unidentified sources (e.g., from ODK Collect 1.1.5 and earlier).</g:CheckBox>
<p><font color="red">Note:</font> checking this box allows malicious
individuals to submit inaccurate data to your server.</p>
<p>Prior to ODK Collect 1.1.6, submitting completed form data did not communicate
the identity of the individual submitting the data to the server.  Unchecking this box
will prevent ODK Collect 1.1.5 and earlier from submitting data to your server.  If left unchecked,
you will need to either:</p>
<ol><li>use ODK Collect 1.1.6 (or higher) configured with user logins enabled or</li>
<li>use the 'Upload Submissions' web page to manually upload the completed submissions</li></ol>
<h2>Google Earth Balloon Display Compatibility</h2>
	<g:CheckBox ui:field="anonymousAttachmentViewers">Allow anonymous
retrieval of images, audio and video data (needed for GoogleEarth ballon displays)</g:CheckBox>
<p>Checking this checkbox enables anyone to access the images, audio clips and video clips
associated with the uploaded form data.  Disclosure risks are somewhat mitigated by needing
to know the exact URL that identifies this data.  It is unlikely that an outsider could guess
that URL, but URLs such as these can be accidentally disclosed by your organization and,
once disclosed, by checking this checkbox, your organization will not have any control
over who can access that data.</p>
	<g:Button  styleName="gwt-Button" ui:field="button" text="Update" />
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 