<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
<g:Label ui:field="insecureAlert" visible="false" 
	styleName="error_message" text="***Site Access Management is Insecure***"/>
<div align="CENTER"><h2>Securing Site Management</h2></div>
<p><font color="red">NOTE:</font> The <em>Manage Website Access</em> tab and this tab are 
incompatible.  If you update the configuration through the <em>Manage Website Access</em>,
any custom changes made through this tab and its subordinate screens will be lost.</p>
<p>Your first task
in securing the site is to restrict access to this page and the other
pages that enable you to control access to the site.  To do this,</p>
<ol>
<li>Define an 'siteAdmins' group, granting it the ROLE_ACCESS_ADMIN permission</li>
<li>Add yourself as a registered user of the site</li>
<li>Add yourself to that 'siteAdmins' group</li>
<li>Log off then log back in (to update your permissions) in order to gain the
 ROLE_ACCESS_ADMIN privilege through the 'siteAdmins' group</li>
<li>Remove the ROLE_ACCESS_ADMIN permission from all other groups</li>
</ol>
<p>After having done this, only you can access these web pages and manage
your site's access permissions.  You should repeat steps 2 and 3 to add
at least one other person to the 'siteAdmins' group.</p>
<h2><g:Label ui:field="earthHeading" text="Google Earth Ballon Image Display Requirements"/></h2>
<p>Google Earth will not display images in the information ballons
unless the ROLE_ATTACHMENT_VIEWER permission is 
granted to USER_IS_ANONYMOUS.</p>
<p>Whether or not
ROLE_ATTACHMENT_VIEWER is assigned to
USER_IS_ANONYMOUS, the images remain
accessible when the user clicks the <em>View</em> link within the information
ballon provided the user has
the necessary privileges to view those images (upon the first such access,
the user may be prompted to log in).</p>
<h2>Further Securing Site Access</h2>
<p>To further secure your site, you need 
to decide which permissions (roles) you want
an anonymous user (someone who has not logged in) to have, which roles you
want users that log in with a gmail.com account to have, and which roles you
want certain specified users to have. The later is accomplished by
defining a group with the roles you want to assign, entering those specified
users into the system as registered users, and assigning them to that group.
</p>
<p>These are exactly the steps you did for the 'siteAdmins' group,
above.</p>
<p>Every registered user automatically belongs to the USER_IS_REGISTERED group;
if you want all registered users to have a given set of roles, then you can
assign those roles to that group.</p>
<table border="1">
<tr><td>Add, remove or modify user groups</td>
<td><g:Anchor ui:field="modifyGroup" text="Manage User Groups" /></td>
<td>Permissions (roles) are granted to user groups. Restrict access 
to your data and website by granting these roles to specific user groups.</td>
</tr>
<tr><td>Add, remove or modify registered users</td>
<td><g:Anchor ui:field="modifyRegisteredUsers" text="Manage Registered Users"/></td>
<td>Permissions can be granted to anonymous users (those not logged in),
to all logged-in users (e.g., anyone with a gmail.com account), and to 
groups of registered users.  Define register users to the system though this web page.</td>
</tr>
<tr><td>Add or remove registered users from user groups</td>
<td>This can be done through either of the above links</td>
<td>Permissions (roles) are granted to user groups.  Users possess the
roles of the groups they belong to.  Manage group memberships to
manage the access rights of the users.</td>
</tr>
<tr><td>Change Aggregate passwords for registered users</td>
<td>This can be done on the <em>Management/Permissions/Manage User Passwords</em> tab</td>
<td>Logins from a device (e.g., ODK Collect) require a password held on this server and
specific to this server (an <em>Aggregate password</em>).
Set or change that password for selected users here. The password is stored
as both a randomly-salted sha-1 hash and as a deterministically-salted md5 hash.
The plaintext password is not retained.</td>
</tr>
</table>		
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 